A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Education, 1975-1997.
Library of Virginia
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 34742), 1990-1994., Extent: 52 cubic feet (52 boxes)
  - VCU - Research Park, 1991. (Box 23)
  - Education - Miscellaneous, 1989. (Box 24)
  - Urban Revitalization, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Science Museum of Western Virginia, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Waiver requests, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous education pamphlets, 1989. (Box 24)
  - Anti-Crime Partnership, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Support letters, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Correspondence, 1991. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Mission, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1993 Apr. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1993 Jan. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1992 Oct. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1992 Apr. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1992 Jan. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Meeting, 1991 Dec. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 Advisory Council - Presentations, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Drop Out Prevention, 1990-1992. (Box 24)
  - Drop Out Prevention - Leadership Council, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Drop Out Prevention - Press releases, 1991. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Meetings, 1992-1993. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Meeting, 1993 Feb. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Meeting, 1992 Nov. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Conference, 1992 Sept. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Meeting, 1992 Mar. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Retreat, 1992 May. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Meeting, 1991 May. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Positions, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partnerships with Higher Education, 1992. (Box 24)
  - Workforce 2000 - National efforts, 1990-1991. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Virginia is for Learners, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Beyer's Committee (HJR 433), 1991. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Developing Competitive Strategies for the 1990s, 1990. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Albemarle / Charlottesville proposal, 1990. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - National legislation, 1991. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Articles, 1991. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Original Task Force, 1990. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Statewide Quality Council (Recommendation 8), 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Business Education (Recommendation 8), 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Publicity campaign, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Virginia Literacy Foundation, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Foundations, 1991. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Leave policy, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 - Legislation, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Advisory Council Resource Notebook, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partners and Programs, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partnership news articles, 19. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partnerships How to, 1990. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partnerships How to, 1991. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program (VBEPP) - Partnerships How to, 1992. (Box 25)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Related legislation, 1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Membership, 1991. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Meeting, 1992 June. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Meeting, 1992 May. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Meeting, 1992 Nov. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Apprenticeships, 1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Concept paper, 1992. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Concept discussions, 1991. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Legislative and communication agenda, 1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Streamlining the State and Federal Education, Employment, and Training Systems (Issue 7), 1992. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Aging Population (Issue 8), 1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Resource policy (Issue 9), undated. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 June. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 May. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 Apr. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 Mar. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 Feb. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1993 Jan. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1992 Dec. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Retreat, 1992 Oct. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1992 Sept. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Retreat, 1992 Sept. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Task Force Meeting, 1992 July. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #1 Welfare Reform and Public Assistance, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #2 Economic Development and Workforce Training, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #3 Inmate Education, Training and Socialization, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #4 Business Productivity, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #5 Literacy Passport / World Class Education, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Workforce 2000 Leadership Council - Agenda #6 Education, Training and Continuum, 1992-1993. (Box 26)
  - Virginia Tidewater Commission, 1990. (Box 26)
  - VQUEST - State assessment, 1987. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Conference, 1991 June. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Partners, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Retreat, 1992 Oct. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Retreat, 1992 Aug. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Retreat, 1992 July. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Contract, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - NSF site visit, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Administration Support Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Assessment Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Community Action Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Education Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Instructional Materials Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Evaluation Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Lead Teacher Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Minorities Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Pre / In Service Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Technology and Communications Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Women and Minorities Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Coordination Component, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Conference, 1993 Feb. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - State and Regional Action Position Paper, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Statewide Action Council, 1993 Apr. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Executive Policy Board, 1993 Apr. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Executive Policy Board, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Governor's Advisory Council, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Related proposals, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - News, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Orbiter, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Liaison Team, 1992. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - National agenda, 1993. (Box 27)
  - VQUEST - Workforce 2000 related studies, 1993. (Box 27)
  - National Governors Association - Publications, 1988-1981. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Proposal, 1991. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - JMU Proposal, 1992. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Seamless web, 1992. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Urban initiatives, 1992. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Science, 1991. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Miscellaneous, 1991. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Science and Technology, 1990-1991. (Box 28)
  - VQUEST - Science Education, 1990. (Box 28)
  - VIP correspondence, 1982. (Box 29)
  - VIP correspondence, 1983. (Box 29)
  - VIP correspondence, 1984. (Box 29)
  - Adams case, 1989. (Box 29)
  - Adams states, 1983. (Box 29)
  - Dept. of Education study: Adams v. Bell, 1982. (Box 29)
  - Adams, 1983. (Box 29)
  - Affirmative Action meetings, 1982, 1986. (Box 29)
  - Affirmative Action - Banquet and speaker, 1986 Feb. (Box 29)
  - Affirmative Action plans, 1985. (Box 29)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Studying Equal Employment Issues at State Supported Colleges and Universities, 1982. (Box 29)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1985. (Box 29)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Virginia Community College System, 1983. (Box 29)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Submissions for Virginia Plan, 1987. (Box 29)
  - Office of Civil Rights - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1984-1987. (Box 29)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Virginia State University, 1990. (Box 29)
  - Cooperative Extension, 1984. (Box 29)
  - State Education Assistance Authority, 1988-1990. (Box 30)
  - Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1983-1990. (Box 30)
  - Adams litigation - Office of Civil Rights, 1982. (Box 30)
  - Divestiture, 1990. (Box 30)
  - Dept. of Education - Adult Education, 1989-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Aids Awareness, 1992-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Alternative education, 1992-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Arts in education, 1991-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Asbestos, 1987-1990. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - At Risk Children, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Aviation education, 1990-1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Compulsory education, 1988-1989. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Chapter I programs, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Composit index, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Confidentiality and Collaboration, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Demonstration projects, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Economics education, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Education for incarcerated adults, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Education in the news, undated. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Elementary schools, 1989-1990. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Education reform, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Efficiency in public education, 1991. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Elected school board issue, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Gifted education programs, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Governor's schools, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Graduation requirements, 1989-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - History and social studies, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Improving math and science education, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Kindergarten entrance age, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Language academics, 1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Learning disabled, 1992-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Literacy, 1990. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Literacy Passport, 1992-1993. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - School funding, 1992. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Education - Local funding for education, 1988-1992. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Magnet schools, 1987. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Medford case, 1991. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Multicultural education, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Newspapers in education, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Other programs, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Prayer in school, 1992. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Pupil transportation issues, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Rate setting, 1992-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Regional Offices Study, 1990. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Rural Virginia, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - School construction, 1990-1991. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - School Health Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - School issues - Cities, 1989-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - School issues - Counties, 1989-1993. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Education - School issues - Race relations, 1991-1993. (Box 32)
  - Project Streamline, 1991-1992. (Box 33)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1989-1990. (Box 33)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1986-1988. (Box 33)
  - School safety, 1992. (Box 33)
  - Radford University, 1990. (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors meetings, 1990-1991. (Box 34)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1990-1992. (Box 34)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1986-1990. (Box 34)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, 1990. (Box 34)
  - Commission for the Arts, 1988-1991. (Box 34)
  - Commission for the Arts - Audit reports, 1987-1989. (Box 34)
  - Roake Museum, 1989-1990. (Box 34)
  - Public Schools - Correspondence (Prince George, Prince William, Radford, Spotsylvania, Sussex, Tazewell), 1989-1992. (Box 35)
  - Special education compliance, 1992. (Box 35)
  - Tazewell Education Network, 1990. (Box 35)
  - Council on Independent Colleges, 1990. (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1988-1992. (Box 35)
  - Genereal Assembly - Legislative proposals, 1993. (Box 35)
  - General Assembly - Legislative proposals, 1992. (Box 35)
  - VIP constituent correspondence (Congress, General Assembly), 1993. (Box 35)
  - Decentralization (HB1144), 1992. (Box 35)
  - Consultants, 1990. (Box 36)
  - Interagency agreements, 1990. (Box 36)
  - Foster care, 1990. (Box 36)
  - Prevention Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 36)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1990. (Box 36)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1991. (Box 36)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1992. (Box 36)
  - Health Care, 1991-1992. (Box 36)
  - General Assembly, 1990. (Box 36)
  - General Assembly, 1991. (Box 36)
  - General Assembly, 1992. (Box 36)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 36)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1991-1992. (Box 36)
  - Education, Dept. of - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 36)
  - Education, Dept. of - General correspondence, 1991. (Box 36)
  - Education, Dept. of - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 36)
  - Training strategies of education, 1992. (Box 37)
  - Girls' Education Advisory Committee, 1990-1992. (Box 37)
  - Girls' Education Advisory Committee, 1991. (Box 37)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1992. (Box 37)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), 1993. (Box 37)
  - Virginiat Student Assistance Authority / State Education Assistance Authority, 1993. (Box 37)
  - Workforce, 1993. (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1993. (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994. (Box 37)
  - Monitoring and Advisory Committee, 1990-1992. (Box 38)
  - Monitoring and Advisory Committee, 1985-1989. (Box 38)
  - VIP correspondence, 1985. (Box 39)
  - Radio Broadcast luncheon, 1985. (Box 39)
  - Office of Civil Rights, 1986. (Box 39)
  - Office of Civil Rights, 1987. (Box 39)
  - Aviation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 40)
  - National Education Commission, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Virginia Community College System, 1990. (Box 40)
  - 1500 hour limitation on wage employees, 1993. (Box 40)
  - Points of Light Foundation, 1993. (Box 40)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Virginia State University, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Science grants, 1991. (Box 40)
  - Peninsula Advanced Technology Development Center, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Interactive Telecommunications, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Articles, 1993. (Box 40)
  - National Voter Registration Act, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Technology - Community Learning and Information Network, 1992. (Box 40)
  - National Alliance of Black School Educators, 1990. (Box 40)
  - Health Workforce 2000, 1993. (Box 40)
  - Shenandoah Valley National Battlefields and Commission, 1993. (Box 40)
  - Project YES - Youth Experiencing Success, 1990-1993. (Box 40)
  - Science Museum of West Virginia and Hopkins Planetarium, 1990. (Box 40)
  - National Governors' Association, 1990-1993. (Box 40)
  - Congress, 1991. (Box 40)
  - Congress, 1992. (Box 40)
  - Congress, 1993. (Box 40)
  - General correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 40)
  - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 40)
  - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 40)
  - School Choice, 1991-1992. (Box 41)
  - Virginia State University, 1992-1993. (Box 41)
  - Campus Civility, 1990. (Box 41)
  - Colleges - Publication Cost surveys, 1990. (Box 41)
  - School Funding - Dropout Prevention Program, 1988-1989. (Box 42)
  - Education Funding, 1993. (Box 43)
  - School Funding - Book I (binder), 1988-1990. (Box 43)
  - School Funding - Book II (binder), 1990. (Box 43)
  - General Assembly Session (binder), 1988. (Box 43)
  - Air and Space Museum (binder), 1990-1992. (Box 43)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - George Mason University, 1991-1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - James Madison University, 1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Museums and miscellaneous, 1991-1993. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Other, 1991-1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Radford University, 1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - University of Virginia, 1991. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - University of Virginia, 1991-1993. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Virginia Commonwealth Universtiy / Medical College of Virginia, 1991. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia, 1991-1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Virginia Tech, 1991. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - Virginia Tech, 1991-1992. (Box 44)
  - Sole Source Procurement Review - William and Mary, 1992. (Box 44)
  - Dropout Prevention Program - General Assembly Appropriation, v. I (binder), 1989. (Box 45)
  - Dropout Prevention Program - General Assembly Appropriation, v. II (binder), 1989. (Box 45)
  - House Appropreations - Budget amendments, v. II (binder), 1990. (Box 45)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1989-1991. (Box 45)
  - Virginia State Archives - Archives Preservation Task Force, 1991. (Box 45)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - The Case for Change, 1989-1991. (Box 46)
  - Higher Education - Consulting contracts, 1990. (Box 46)
  - Higher Education - Administrative decentralization, 1986-1992. (Box 46)
  - Virginia Community College System - Consolidation, 1991. (Box 46)
  - Virginia Community College System - Tidewater Community College, Norfolk Campus, 1992. (Box 46)
  - Virginia State University - Presidency, 1993. (Box 46)
  - Virginia State University - Correspondence, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
  - University of Virginia - Curry School of Education, 1990-1991. (Box 47)
  - Old Dominion University, 1989-1990. (Box 47)
  - Old Dominion University - President's House, 1989. (Box 47)
  - Mary Washington College, 1989. (Box 47)
  - Norfolk State University, 1990. (Box 47)
  - Norfolk State University - Land purchase, 1986-1988. (Box 47)
  - James Madison University - Valley Construction, 1990. (Box 47)
  - James Madison University, 1989-1990. (Box 47)
  - Longwood College, 1990-191. (Box 47)
  - Christopher Newport, 1990. (Box 47)
  - Clinch Valley College of UVA, 1990. (Box 47)
  - General Finance / Revenue, 1992-1993. (Box 48)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension, 1990-1992. (Box 48)
  - Transfer Students Conference, 1991. (Box 48)
  - Continuous Electronic Beam Accellerator Facility (CEBAF), 1984-1990. (Box 48)
  - Continuous Electronic Beam Accellerator Facility (CEBAF), 1991. (Box 48)
  - Continuous Electronic Beam Accellerator Facility (CEBAF), 1992-1993. (Box 48)
  - Virginia Community College System - Salary Supplements, 1986. (Box 48)
  - Virginia Community College System - Salary Supplements, 1987-1988. (Box 48)
  - Virginia Community College System - Salary Supplements, 1988-1989. (Box 48)
  - Virginia Community College System - Salary Supplements, 1990-1991. (Box 48)
  - University correspondence, 1989-1990. (Box 48)
  - VCU Expansion - Master Site Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 49)
  - SEAA and US Dept of Education, 1988-1991. (Box 49)
  - University of Virginia, 1989-1990. (Box 49)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1989-1990. (Box 50)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1989-1990. (Box 50)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1990-1991. (Box 50)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Veterinary School, 1983-1990. (Box 50)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Service, 1985-1989. (Box 50)
  - Virginia State University, 1988-1992. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University, 1990. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University, 1991. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Maintenance repair project, 1984-1989. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Enhancement / Expenditure Plans, 1985-1989. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Board of Visitors, 1986. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Nursing Home Program, 1984-1987. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Dormitories, 1987-1988. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Aquaculture Program, 1986. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Master Plan, 1985-1988. (Box 51)
  - Virginia State University - Board Retreat, 1985. (Box 51)
  - School Breakfast / Lunch, 1992. (Box 52)
  - School uniforms, 1991. (Box 52)
  - Serial writers, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Schools, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Education - Standards of Quality, 1993. (Box 52)
  - Statewide Assessment and Curriculum, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Teacher Education / Preparation, 1993. (Box 52)
  - Teacher salaries, 1989-1991. (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Education - University Research Consortium, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Virginia is for Learners, 1992. (Box 52)
  - World Class Education Initiative, 1992-1993. (Box 52)
  - Year Round Schools, 1990-1992. (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Education - Vocational / Technical Education, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Virginia High School League, 1991. (Box 52)
  - Youth Apprenticeship, 1992. (Box 52)
  - Dept. of Education - Youth Risk Behavior, 1993. (Box 52)
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 35868), 1994-1997., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes)
  - General correspondence, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - Speeches, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Education, Dept. of, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Arts, Commission for the, 1995-1996. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Fine Arts, Virginia Museum of, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Frontier Culture Museum, 1995-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Gunston Hall, 1994-1995. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1995-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Library of Virginia, 1994-1996. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Science Museum, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 1995-1997. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Virginia Advisory Council on Adult Education and Literacy, 1996. (Box 1)
  - State Agencies: Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1994-1996. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Institutions: Christopher Newport University, 1994-1996. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Institutions: Clinch Valley College, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Institutions: George Mason University, 1995-1997. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Institutions: James Madison University, 1994-1997. (Box 1)
  - Higher Education Institutions: Longwood College, 1994-1997. (Box 1)